LOOKING FOR THE SEX VIDEO OF THIS GIRL
DO YOU KNOW THIS GIRL?
IT'S HARD TO GET HER VIDEO
HEARD SHE KILLED HERSELF
YOU REALLY WANNA JACK OFF TO THIS?
BUT I SAW A PIC OF HER
WORKING AS A FLORIST
"Why can't you take my word for it
and just believe me? She's dead."
SHE'S DEAD. THE FLORIST THING IS A LIE.
A KILLER PARADOX
RESIDENT IDENTIFICATION CERTIFICATE
LEE GYEONG-SU
Superman flies through the sky.
Spider-Man shoots out webs.
And Lee Tang carries out retribution.
Those who are detected on Lee Tang's radar
are all criminals
who dodged laws made by men.
-And deserved to die.
-Bitch.
-No, they're all human garbage.
-What do you want?
Professor, please.
If you got pregnant, then you should've
gotten an abortion. So go!
It's your baby, though.
Stupid whore! How dare you?
MURDERED PROFESSOR WAS A KILLER
Retribution isn't bound
by laws or ethics. It's pure and absolute.
A crime always leaves behind evidence,
but retribution is beyond
something humans can prove.
Emotions will get the better of
he who murders for vengeance,
and punishment
for those who murder in malice.
But Lee Tang's murders are not
swayed by emotions or punishment.
They are the essence of pure good
and absolute justice.
No one can take these criminals to trial,
but someone must act,
even though not a person
in the world will ever know about it.
Gyeong-su, what'd you do
before this? Were you a student?
No.
You wanna open up your own store, or what?
Oh… So, then, why'd you come
all this way out to Busan?
You know, these Gen Z kids hate it
when you bombard them with questions.
-That's not true. They enjoy it.
-You can just ignore her.
Gyeong-a, we're a family here.
Why are you acting this way?
Seon-gyeong is home until tomorrow
because she's sick.
I'm not asking for a huge favor.
Shouldn't you be hiring
a new cashier then, sir?
-Oh my God. There she goes again.
-Are you serious? Really?
-We need all the help we can get!
-Kids these days are all so rude.
-Doesn't care about anyone but herself.
-Come on, get serious.
-Honestly!
-Yes, but…
She's the worst. Since she started,
I don't think she's ever said hello.
And she never goes out with us.
Hey, the girl's probably
just busy with her boyfriend.
Are you making a fuss 'cause she's pretty?
Hah! What do you mean, pretty?
She's probably had her whole face done.
And what's the point of plastic surgery
when you're stuck in a warehouse?
Okay, I'll get it done after this.
It's always "after this." I'll do it.
No one's at the register. Get to it.
Please, okay? Thank you.
Oh, Seung-hun.
"The homeroom rep
and Choi In-seon fought today."
"The homeroom rep totally made fun of her
and said the mole on her nose
looks like a weird booger."
The homeroom rep had
a crush on her too.
A love triangle?
Pfft. That's adorable.
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO CELEBRATE
-Oppa.
-Mm-hmm?
-When are you gonna be done?
-Oh, whoa!
-Do you still have a lot to do?
-Why?
-How much do you have left?
-Mm?
When will you be done?
I'm all done. I'm all done.
-Finished.
-Aren't I heavy?
Not at all. Why can't you
just leave me alone, hmm?
-Kiss me. Kiss me.
-What took you so long, huh?
Excuse me!
This is exactly like last time.
This supermarket has terrible service.
What, do you think your work's
done after you sell the goods? Huh?
Customers have to keep
a stupid file of receipts now?
You say you bought this three days ago?
Forget it, come on!
I'm busy. Just hurry already.
Hey, if you don't know, just ask. Come on!
I'm searching for the purchase
you made to print the receipt for you,
but I don't see it here.
What the hell are you mumbling about?
Where else do you think I would've bought
this crap, if it wasn't from here?
What are you looking at?
Don't give me that look, you little hussy!
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
-Come on, then!
-Ma'am.
I'm sorry. I think she just
made a mistake.
-Give her a refund
-What's with this supermarket?
All I did was ask for a refund!
Ma'am, I'll make sure
this doesn't happen again. I'm so sorry.
Thank you for understanding.
Here, this is on the house.
I'm sorry again.
Drive safely.
What?
Hey. Hey, did you do
this to my windshield?
Have you completely
lost your damn mind? Huh?
Are you crazy?
I asked you a question! Jeez.
What if I didn't do it?
Will you say sorry?
What?
You shouldn't accuse
if you don't have any proof.
I guess you're too ignorant
and dumb to know better,
but you messed with the wrong lady.
I have a dashcam.
I'm not letting this slide.
-Are you nuts? Unbelievable!
-Fine, report it.
I'm sure the dashcam caught you stealing
from that pile and demanding a refund.
What?
Make your call.
I'm…
-Should I call?
-Hey. What are you doing?
-I don't have time for this!
-Well?
It's…
it's not that.
Then what? Huh?
You won't even answer the customers
when they ask a question.
Why do you act this way? Huh?
I told you about this last time.
I'm sorry.
-Fish section, right?
-Yeah.
Why'd you come here?
Listen.
I think you're a lot like me, actually.
I am?
You know, I've been noticing how…
how you change the subject
when they ask about your past,
and how you keep your
distance from others.
And you're probably in your 20s,
but got a job at a small supermarket
that's really far away.
Aah.
And, uh, you're rude to asshole customers.
I feel like…
like we have that in common.
I'm like that, huh?
Well, if not, forget it.
Aren't you tired of people here
being gossipy
and in your business all the time?
Although, they're not all that bad,
to be honest.
Mm… They normally nag
you and act annoying.
Except they usually quit
after the first month that you're here.
I didn't get to have that, though,
so it's hard.
What's that?
Well, being, I guess, normal.
I mean, living a normal life.
You know, I'm just kinda…
tired of having big dreams anymore.
Just… living an ordinary life
seems to be the key.
Please take a step back
from the yellow line.
I repeat.
The KTX train scheduled
to arrive in Busan at 9:50 a.m…
LOOKING FOR THE SEX VIDEO OF THIS GIRL
DO YOU KNOW THIS GIRL?
IS THIS HER?
…from the yellow line.
UPDATE ON THE GIRL
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION
THE REPUBLIC OF PLASTIC SURGERY
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
Mom! Mom.
Hey, come help me with these.
Why'd you bring all this? You should've
just had it all shipped over.
The move must have you pretty busy.
Why ship it when I can just bring it?
How's that going?
Are you doing door-to-door service?
No. Don't you know
how far we're moving?
Are you nuts? How are you gonna do it all?
I'm just organizing
and throwing stuff out.
Think it's easy starting a new life?
Gosh.
So, did Dad head there already?
What about In-jun?
They both went
to finish the greenhouse.
Check if that's yours.
Hey, what'd you bring these for?
What's this doing here?
I had it terminated
at the community service center.
Remember, you got another one
because you had lost it?
I found that one in the closet.
IDENTIFICATION
CHOI IN-SEON, CHOI GYEONG-A
Gyeong-a.
You'll visit us often, right?
Hmm?
You don't need a reason
to come home, you know.
Why are you suddenly bringing that up now?
We have a room for you in the new house.
Now you can visit whenever you want.
Think of it more like a fun sabbatical.
Hey.
Look at you. You're
glowin' after a little time off. Jesus.
You haven't even opened it.
Didn't you get that last summer?
You got a nice place,
but you need a woman in here.
Smells like a bachelor pad.
Whoa! What--
Hey, isn't this the…
the dog from that girl's case?
Dang, well, we can't just
send him away somewhere.
We can't put him down, either.
Should a detective raise a dog, though?
I brought him here
hoping he might bring me luck
with all of the ongoing investigations.
I'm just keeping him
until he's proven innocent.
Didn't you say you have some time
before you leave? Why are you here?
Well, it's what's-his-face.
Right, Roh Bin.
Don't go near him, all right?
It's thanks to the captain
you only got a restraining order.
If he decides to press charges
against you, your ass is done for, buddy.
How am I supposed to investigate when
I can't even get his security cam footage?
You came here to tell me that?
No. Listen.
You…
Look, why aren't
you answering anybody's calls?
Did Yong-jae say I wasn't pickin' up?
He keeps on callin' me
'cause you never answer.
So?
-So I told him to come.
-Come where? Here?
-Now?
-Yeah.
You owe me, sir.
I'm really sorry
about the Kang Sang-muk incident.
And I only received a warning
because you kept me in the dark
about the situation
at Roh Bin's house, right?
But if you had trusted me, sir,
and shared information
for the investigation,
we might've caught both Lee Tang
and that nerd without getting suspended.
I'm so frustrated that I can't even sleep.
I'm gonna catch that asshole, sir.
Look how much he has to say.
Imagine how upset he was you ignored him.
There you go. Good.
Imagine that there's a line between here,
and cut across in one go.
That's it! Yeah, great.
-Look at that.
-Oh, God.
He just needs to clean. What the heck
are you teaching him all that for?
You should come check him out.
He got the bones out perfectly.
This right here is not an easy task.
-Yeah, he's okay.
-This is how you learn.
It's awkward and kinda tricky at first,
but then, after a little practice,
you get used to it, hmm?
You keep goin' like that,
and you'll be able
to open up a shop in no time.
So keep at it, kid.
Heard about
Professor No's murder in Busan?
Yeah.
When he disappeared that day,
he moved to Busan. Lee Tang.
Hmm.
Oh, we found this by chance
while working on another case.
-Huh! Chance, my ass.
-Well, did you know?
Hey, look at this.
This right here is
the murder of a drug dealer in Busan,
and this, over here,
is the loan shark murder case.
Hey, that…
that guy was murdered by a junkie,
and the other guy died in a gang fight.
And they couldn't find the culprit
for either case.
So, what are you gonna do, then?
Do you even have a warrant?
I know.
We should go to Busan first.
The cases in Daejeon are all closed now.
And we don't have an APB on him.
Are you any good with emotional appeals?
If I were the one reading this letter,
I'd feel worried and perplexed also, yeah.
-They told us he's an adult.
-Yeah.
That he said
he was planning to take a working holiday,
and that he even left a letter.
So they suggested that we report him
as a runaway, not as missing.
-Mm-hmm.
-So we just left.
Yes, um…
I want you to know
that you can legally report him missing.
What? I don't get it. What's going on?
How come the cops are saying two different
things about the same exact case?
-Do they have different laws?
-This must be confusing--
-Honey, no, please. I--
-They want to help us, all right? Please.
-So, what is it that you'd like from us?
-Uh-huh.
Uh, well, you can start
by reporting him missing again to me.
If there's even a small chance
that someone is connected to a crime,
then you can report them missing.
-That's even--
-Wait.
-Are you telling us he's a victim?
-No, that's not exactly what I'm saying.
-What are you saying?
-Are you saying he committed a crime?
-Uh…
-Hmm?
As you can see right here, very well,
he even asked
if we could use his security deposit
to pay the store owner.
-That's who he is.
-Yes. I see.
-How can a kid like that commit a crime?
-Yes, I'm saying your son--
What about… What do you call it?
Uh, voice phishing?
-Or a cult or something? Is that what he--
-Ah, no, sir, it's not that.
-You don't--
-Stop talking nonsense!
So, what I think is
you need to find your son.
-Of course.
-Yeah.
-That is the most crucial thing right now.
-Exactly.
-Right.
-This is frustrating.
All right, guys. Let's just
hear them out first. You…
You're not here to help us, are you?
-I, uh… We'll help you find--
-No.
No.
We've actually come here
to ask you for your help.
Then please, just be honest with us here.
And then we'll make a decision.
Like your mom said,
he doesn't have the guts to do that. Huh?
-Mm…
-I know exactly how these cops operate.
They go poking around
just based on a hunch.
Don't worry too much.
I thought they were strange too.
How could they think…
This whole thing's just ridiculous.
Mom has a good point.
Uh, Ma, I'm gonna go, okay?
-Can you take a look at this for me?
-Hmm?
Do you get something like this
even if you're abroad?
RESERVE FORCES TRAINING NOTIFICATION
TO MR. LEE TANG
BUSAN STATION
Mm, this is delicious.
Your dad hates this type of food.
I only eat at places like this with you.
Well, enjoy. You still
have time before your train.
-Hmm?
-Your brother's just like your dad.
He never takes me to nice places.
-My daughter's the best.
-I wonder what it'll be tomorrow.
You're addicted at this point.
Seriously.
No, I'm not.
Ugh. It's seven already.
I really don't wanna go back to Seoul.
-Drink water.
-I--
Eat while it's hot.
I'm sorry about this.
I tried,
but I just can't let this one slide.
Hey.
-Wait, aren't you--
-What are you staring at? Hmm?
What's mesmerizing enough to make you
keep staring at someone while they eat?
-What is it?
-No, no, I'm not--
Seeing a girl from a sex video
in real life got you turned on? That it?
-Wait, uh, that's not why I stared.
-Oh, no?
Why, huh? You little shits
can't even talk about it outright.
-I thought you were someone I knew.
-Yes, I'm her.
-I'm the girl in the video.
-No, that's not… It's just, uh…
You went to Kwonseong Elementary.
Aren't you Choi In-seon?
It's me, Ha Sang-min.
Well, um…
Your mom,
she owned the snack shop near school.
Yeah. And she looked familiar, so…
Mm.
So, when did you come down to Busan?
It was about, um,
this time last year, I think, so…
-I see.
-I'm going back to Seoul next year.
Oh, you are?
Still, you were here for a while. Mm.
Did something go down?
I hadn't heard anything, but…
Yeah, you heard it tonight, already.
So, that's that. Mm.
Hmm.
You, um, removed your mole, didn't you?
Ah, that's right.
That was the first thing
I took care of.
Oh, booger face!
Wait, you don't remember?
What did you say?
-Booger face! You know?
-What?
I recently read my childhood journal,
a little while ago,
and, um… I had written about you.
And it reminded me
of that little booger joke.
What?
Ah, come on.
How come you still have that old journal?
It's nice to walk down memory lane.
Right by the beach. Nice.
Thanks for the ride.
I can get home by myself from here.
-Mm.
-Sorry about earlier today.
No, it's cool.
Hey, is it okay if we stay in touch?
Oh… actually…
Let's not see each other anymore.
I think I'd be more comfortable with that.
I gotta go. See ya.
Bye.
How can I help you, ma'am?
Hello.
Hi, ma'am. Thanks for coming.
-We brought you this.
-Oh, right, right. Thank you.
REQUESTING COOPERATION
IN MISSING PERSON SEARCH
Lee Tang. Lee Tang?
His name is Lee Tang?
-Yeah.
-That's a pretty unique name, huh?
So this kid who went AWOL in Daejeon,
this is the guy who killed No Ui-cheol?
Yes.
We realize you're busy, but could you
please help us out just this once?
Yeah, we are very busy.
And regarding
Professor No Ui-cheol's murder,
we're doing everything we can right now.
We identified a suspect
who he's on bad terms with.
-Our boys are out on a stakeout now.
-I see.
They're practically living at the station
and the scene,
trying to find the murder weapon
and witnesses,
really giving it their all,
and their wives want 'em back already.
And…
And now, you come in here saying
this missing person is a suspect.
Without any leads.
Wouldn't that put us in a tough position--
We have an official document issued
for your cooperation, so…
We'd appreciate if you would work with us.
-Yes, but we're busy--
-All right.
We just have to let you know
if something comes up with those murders?
Yeah. Uh, no.
We'd really appreciate it if, uh…
if you could share information
about any unnatural deaths too.
-Everything?
-Yeah.
All I've ever done is work.
That's not a sin.
My daughter just started middle school.
What did I do wrong? Huh?
Answer me, you bitch.
For fuck's sake, man.
These pricks are impossible.
Whoops.
How long do you think you can evade us?
Yeah, hello?
Gyeong-a, it's Sang-min.
We hung out a few days ago.
Can you talk for a second?
How were you able to find my number?
Well, I asked some of our friends
if they had it,
and then I asked around to some
other people from elementary school.
I thought I was clear.
I don't want to talk to you.
But there's something I need to tell you.
What is it?
I got sextorted.
I…
I have no idea what to do right now.
Just tell me the truth.
How did you find my number, really?
Well, I was desperate… to get your number,
so I asked my cop friend for it.
I realize it was wrong.
It was my only option.
I thought you could help.
'Cause I thought
this could really be the end.
It's not like
I can just
go to Seoul or anything.
I can't even contact my parents right now.
It's awful.
I just…
Right, that's a good call.
It's expensive,
but hiring a private service is better.
And cops are just not reliable.
My girlfriend wanted to end things.
So we did.
I don't know what to tell my parents.
That's it.
Just be thankful that it hasn't
gotten out any more than it has.
So, how did you get through it?
Huh?
How did you get over it?
Get over it? Yeah.
You saw me the other day.
I'm suspicious of every man
who looks in my direction.
"Has he already seen my video?"
So, yeah.
I still haven't really gotten over it,
exactly.
Gyeong-a.
Hmm?
You can't blame yourself for it.
You just can't.
You're doing really great.
Hey, since you drove here,
you can go when you're sober.
-Here, if you wanna shower.
-Right, thanks.
You wanna sleep here?
Babe, did something good happen?
Why do you look like that?
It's nothing. I'm just happy.
What?
What's with you?
-It's good.
-Going back in two days?
-I think I'm going tomorrow.
-Again?
Mm-hmm. The boss asked me
to work and help him out.
So I said I would.
It sucks, but we're getting married soon,
so I should be diligent.
-I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
I'll take you someplace nice
next time.
Hey. Open up your trunk.
-Why?
-Just open it.
Why?
Oppa!
-What?
-Why'd you lie to me?
You've got a terrible poker face.
-I wasn't lying.
-You could've said you were going fishing.
I wouldn't have gotten angry.
I'm really not that petty.
Just go.
Go have fun with your friends, okay?
-I just didn't wanna hurt your feelings.
-Oppa! Let's always be honest, okay?
I want us to tell the truth
to avoid issues down the line.
-All right?
-Yes. You're right.
We're getting married,
so I'll let this one go.
You won't find a girl like me.
Treat me right!
Okay, I'll do better.
Let's go!
I'm here
to get groceries with the guys. Yeah.
Yeah, I miss you too, babe.
I found a coffee shop here
that you'd love. It even has a terrace.
Yes.
I love you too. Bye.
I'll call you back, okay?
Bye.
Gyeong-a.
What? I thought
you said you were in Seoul.
I wanted to surprise you.
Oh…
The warmth
of another person's embrace.
I don't know
how I've gone so long without it.
Mm-hmm.
It's really amazing
how childhood friends can fall in love.
Should I
come back with you when you go to Seoul?
Seoul?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you live in Seoul, so I…
Hang on.
I'm tired.
NOT BAD
BUT WHY IS THE VIDEO SO SHORT?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO CELEBRATE
What are you doing?
Give me back my phone.
What the hell?
Didn't you say that you…
…broke up with your girlfriend?
I was gonna tell you.
-I didn't get a chance.
-When?
I was gonna tell you.
I thought you were going out with me
because you already ended things.
Listen, In-seon.
-It's Gyeong-a now!
-Okay, fine, I know! Gyeong-a, come on!
I'm telling you now!
Telling me what, exactly?
Just tell me
everything you lied about right now.
What's really going on here?
Oh, now we're in business.
DELIVERY
MS. CHOI GYEONG-A
This camera's great. Honey!
-Look over here.
-What are you doing?
You know. Come on, it's fun.
What? Is this a video? Stop it.
-What?
-Oh, my In-seon.
-We're making memories.
-Just for us?
So she wanted to?
Did you really get sextorted?
Why would
you look at my phone? Fuck.
Tell me if that was real or not,
right now.
All right, yeah.
I made it up to sleep with you.
You don't see me as a human. Is that it?
-I'm just a piece of meat?
-Ugh, fucking bitch.
-That you fuck and just walk away? Huh?
-Hey!
-Listen, God damn it! Now!
-What? What? What?
-You knew I had a girlfriend!
-What?
Hey! You invited me into your bed!
So stop whining, you bitch.
You said you broke up with her!
-Shut the fuck up.
-Fine. All right, fine.
Let's say I knew.
Does your girlfriend know?
-Does she know you're having sex with me?
-Are you seriously threatening me?
-Do your colleagues know?
-So you're threatening me?
Yes, I am. Where's your phone?
-Your girlfriend and friends should know!
-Stop that.
You stupid little bitch.
You fucking asshole!
For fuck's sake!
Hey!
Hey, stop it.
You fucking little bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
You fucking bitch!
Shit! Can't you…
CHOI IN-SEON, CHOI GYEONG-A
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no.
What do I do? What do I do? What the fuck?
The exact cause of the fire
and the number of casualties
is still currently being investigated.
The fire department sent 12 firefighters
and used several pieces of equipment
as soon as they received the report
and were able to extinguish the fire
within one hour.
They have said that the cause of the fire
is still under investigation.
Busanjin Police Station
identified the victim
as a 29-year-old female
residing in Gyeongnam.
Based on witness statements
and the security camera footage--
-Around 5:00 a.m. today…
-Isn't that our neighborhood?
-Hang on. Where did you say that was?
-It's across from Gujeon Church.
-Gujeon Church.
-Gujeon?
-Yeah. I heard the lady lived alone.
-Oh wow. This is awful.
Know what else I heard? She was murdered.
-Come on!
-Really?
-Uh-huh.
-Stop spreading ridiculous rumors.
Neighbors heard her
fighting with someone all night.
-No way.
-Who said that?
Do-jun's mother.
You know that woman's always full of crap
and making stuff up.
-Well, I don't totally believe her.
-See? Even you're not sure.
-My God.
-I know. So tragic.
Let it go.
Well, then.
…possibility of the fire being arson…
How much do you believe her?
-The city of Busan is…
-Huh?
VICTIM CHOI GYEONG-A
Well, it seems like
the girl was just drunk
and just forgot to turn off the stove
before she went to bed.
Also, we, uh,
looked through her call history,
and she only kept in touch
with her parents.
The other people on the list were,
uh, just… What was it? Her coworkers…
-Oh, yeah, and the delivery man.
-Who is this?
-I think…
-It's her friend.
He didn't call on the day of the incident.
So chances of her being a murder victim
are low,
but we're doing an autopsy, so we'll see.
Can we start the investigation?
-What investigation? We have no warrant.
-There are procedures.
I'm saying we should be open
to the idea that this was actually murder.
Okay? I wanted you to share everything.
You think all dead bodies
are murders cases?
-God!
-Fuck! Shit.
Hey, Gyeong-su. There you are.
-Hey, give me the phone.
-Here.
You know, uh, that girl, right?
Yeah, you know her. Gyeong-a.
Why? What's going on?
BODY FOUND
This is her.
Apparently, she, uh… died.
-Hey. Come here.
-Huh?
Yeah. Okay. Get to work.
All right. Come on, guys.
Enough with this, already, huh?
Now, we should just…
-Yes, great job.
-No, look…
Maybe next week.
-Wait here.
-Yes, sir.
Where is he?
-Wait, why's he looking for him?
-He's police.
Hey, where you going?
Oh! Ah!
Lee Tang.
I can't believe how sloppy you are.
You know the case in Gujeon-dong?
It was you, huh?
Oh, stand up, huh?
We gotta go somewhere now.
There's a lot we gotta talk about, kid.
Just the two of us.
-I manage the security cameras.
-Yong-jae.
-What's wrong?
-Hey.
-Someone stole the security footage drive.
-The cameras?
-Yeah.
-You got a manual for this?
-Let me see the photo.
-Who's in charge?
I manage it all.
-They're just for monitoring employees.
-Have you seen this person?
Is this Gyeong-su?
-I think he works here.
-He works here? Do you have his address?
-Yeah, I have it.
-Let's go here first.
Hey, hold on.
This isn't your turf.
He's a murder suspect.
We should visit him.
Are you kidding me right now?
Listen, man.
I did some digging, and apparently,
you got suspended in Daejeon.
I looked the other way since you're
one of us, but stay in your lane.
I was looking into a guy in a murder case.
-I was suspended--
-How can we trust a suspended detective?
What's not to trust?
I have no reason to lie.
Besides, we got nothin' to lose anymore.
-There are procedures and orders we need--
-Stop it. Come on.
This man.
You're sure that he's your employee?
Yeah, in the fish section.
Okay. I say we all go.
Follow me.
What?
Look at this punk.
-Kwak, go and see Ha Sang-min.
-Yes, sir.
-The delivery man, as well.
-Okay, you got it.
-You get all footage near the house.
-Hey. Come here.
Follow Detective Kwak's interviews.
-Not Lee Tang?
-I'll do that.
Stay close with them
and report back on what they're all up to.
-…all needs to be done now.
-Hurry.
-Come on.
-Uh, okay. I'll call you.
It's called Neisseria gonorrhoeae.
You have heard of gonorrhea, haven't you?
It's a bacteria,
transmitted through sexual intercourse.
But there's no need to worry.
It can be fully cured with antibiotics.
Oh, and no sexual intercourse
for the time being.
I was in bed sick.
Honey, I got some not great news.
Babe, wait.
No, let me… let me talk first.
Hmm? What is it?
I have gonorrhea.
Just how…
I wanted to bring it up to you first, but…
-Hmm.
-I'm so sorry, baby.
It was a mistake. It only happened once.
-What are you saying?
-I wasn't even gonna go.
But my friends were insisting
I'm not gonna have fun anymore
once I'm married.
They literally just dragged me along.
Oppa, I'm so sorry.
It was really just a stupid mistake.
Wow.
-You're a fucking bitch.
-What?
-Huh.
-Oh…
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Hyeon-ji.
-Just fuck off.
-Oppa--
Shit, man.
Mr. Ha Sang-min?
-Yes?
-Ah.
You know Choi Gyeong-a. Isn't that right?
-Yeah.
-And you went to Gujeon-dong.
Yeah.
-And you slept with her.
-Yes.
-But you didn't kill her?
-Right.
Hmm.
So you found out
from the news she was dead?
Yes.
That so?
Why was she killed?
Because, from what I heard, there were
sounds of fighting at her apartment.
Uh…
At what time?
I don't know, um… anything about that.
From now on,
let's not lie anymore.
Unless you wanna
complicate the matter at hand.
Oh. I… I remember now. I, uh…
Actually, I'd started dated Gyeong-a
while I had a girlfriend still.
And Gyeong-a had known that
going into the relationship.
But… she eventually happened to learn
that I, uh…
-Uh… was actually engaged… to her.
-Okay.
-Ah.
-So, that…
I guess it made her feel lied to,
and she raised her voice.
-Aah.
-That brought on an argument.
And?
You beat her head in? Like that?
What are you… No.
I really didn't kill her.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
You fucking asshole.
I was thinking about setting you free.
Shameless. It's true, huh?
Almost had me fooled.
You're so, so brazen.
Do you have a warrant for that?
-A what?
-I said, do you have a warrant for that?
Right.
-Uh…
-What?
I'd like my attorney present
for when you take my statement.
It's always you half-assed idiots, huh?
-Huh?
-I want my lawyer.
Run your mouths, hmm?
It's fine. You won't get caught.
I didn't even kill her. Fuck.
But… I kinda ran away.
If what you're saying is true,
I should stay in Busan.
Now it's different.
That hunch you felt
could be part of your powers.
But if you feel that way again,
you gotta be cautious.
You should probably lay low.
Don't contact me. Turn your phone off.
I'll see what I can do, okay?
Let's see…
Ugh, come on.
Why isn't there any paper
in this dumb, shitty house?
You're not…
you're not a cop, are you?
I am.
Well, used to be.
Why… why are you doing this?
All right, let me ask you a question.
There's this
bastard I'm trying to locate.
That dumbass
somehow zeroes in on shitheads like you
and kills them, huh?
Then, shouldn't he be
already well on his way,
you little shit stain?
This is boring.
So boring.
Will you not kill me
if I tell you the truth?
What?
Will I keep you alive, you said?
Yes.
So you admit you killed her, then?
Yeah.
All right, go ahead.
Write it.
Uh…
Choi In-seon…
I, HA SANG-MIN, MURDERED CHOI IN-SEON,
AND I SHOW MY REMORSE THROUGH DEATH
Huh.
He didn't say how he killed Gyeong-a.
God.
Can't do much writing now.
Shit.
God, he just has no common sense.
Apology letters should always state
the when, why, and how.
Damn millennials.
This is the apartment
management office.
There was a fire recently due to
an induction cooktop in one of the units.
When leaving the house, please be sure
to turn off the cooktop
or unplug it entirely.
Additionally, do not leave
paper towels near the cooktop,
as it may cause a fire.
That Lee Tang, or Lee Gyeong-su,
he's probably already left Busan.
He had to have left some clues behind.
Something helpful.
That's true. He didn't have time
to stop at his house.
There's gotta be something there.
Anyone there?
Hello?
Anyone home?
Is this the management office?
It's the police.
Where's the master key for this place?
Huh?
It was stolen? By who?
What do you mean?
Don't you hear that sound?
No, what sound? I don't hear it.
FUEL
DO NOT HEAT
What the…
What's with all this smoke?
Is that from a fire extinguisher?
Has he been by already?